{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073090194","data":{"timestamp":" 947073090194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145115"," gameId":" c63338d4-5bd0-4e0e-83c7-eb3b0f4be5eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ponuvi_fekewa-rinoke-ponuvi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ponuvi"," userResponse":" ponuvi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073099312","data":{"timestamp":" 947073099311"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145115"," gameId":" c63338d4-5bd0-4e0e-83c7-eb3b0f4be5eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sujuye_vitezu-sujuye-jowoma"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sujuye"," userResponse":" sujuye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073104946","data":{"timestamp":" 947073104946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145115"," gameId":" c63338d4-5bd0-4e0e-83c7-eb3b0f4be5eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_walimu_lununa-walimu-yulefo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" walimu"," userResponse":" walimu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073111013","data":{"timestamp":" 947073111013"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145115"," gameId":" c63338d4-5bd0-4e0e-83c7-eb3b0f4be5eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sovipa_hufuvo-sujuye-sovipa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sovipa"," userResponse":" sujuye"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073117079","data":{"timestamp":" 947073117079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145115"," gameId":" c63338d4-5bd0-4e0e-83c7-eb3b0f4be5eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sovipa_hufuvo-sujuye-sovipa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sovipa"," userResponse":" sovipa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073122209","data":{"timestamp":" 947073122209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145115"," gameId":" c63338d4-5bd0-4e0e-83c7-eb3b0f4be5eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lorewi_jezipi-lorewi-bodabi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lorewi"," userResponse":" lorewi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073127707","data":{"timestamp":" 947073127707"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145115"," gameId":" c63338d4-5bd0-4e0e-83c7-eb3b0f4be5eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_rutiza_fihulu-mozagu-rutiza"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" rutiza"," userResponse":" rutiza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073133844","data":{"timestamp":" 947073133844"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145115"," gameId":" c63338d4-5bd0-4e0e-83c7-eb3b0f4be5eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vomuzo_bodabi-vomuzo-zojuwu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vomuzo"," userResponse":" vomuzo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073138924","data":{"timestamp":" 947073138923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145115"," gameId":" c63338d4-5bd0-4e0e-83c7-eb3b0f4be5eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_yenake_yenake-zojuwu-veweho"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" yenake"," userResponse":" yenake"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073148111","data":{"timestamp":" 947073148111"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145115"," gameId":" c63338d4-5bd0-4e0e-83c7-eb3b0f4be5eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fihulu_peyake-hufuvo-fihulu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fihulu"," userResponse":" fihulu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073154632","data":{"timestamp":" 947073154632"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145115"," gameId":" c63338d4-5bd0-4e0e-83c7-eb3b0f4be5eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tafemi_tafemi-rutiza-sovipa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tafemi"," userResponse":" tafemi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073160409","data":{"timestamp":" 947073160407"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145115"," gameId":" c63338d4-5bd0-4e0e-83c7-eb3b0f4be5eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_tafemi_tafemi-rutiza-sovipa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073184360","data":{"timestamp":" 947073184360"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145115"," gameId":" 72e48d99-3331-4436-a36b-e91e852811f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pazaba_tuvari-pazaba-jezipi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pazaba"," userResponse":" tuvari"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073191372","data":{"timestamp":" 947073191372"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145115"," gameId":" 72e48d99-3331-4436-a36b-e91e852811f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pazaba_tuvari-pazaba-jezipi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pazaba"," userResponse":" pazaba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073197233","data":{"timestamp":" 947073197233"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145115"," gameId":" 72e48d99-3331-4436-a36b-e91e852811f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tuvari_voriza-tuvari-jowoma"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tuvari"," userResponse":" tuvari"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073203589","data":{"timestamp":" 947073203589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145115"," gameId":" 72e48d99-3331-4436-a36b-e91e852811f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_rinoke_rinoke-limame-jowoma"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" rinoke"," userResponse":" rinoke"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073208524","data":{"timestamp":" 947073208524"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145115"," gameId":" 72e48d99-3331-4436-a36b-e91e852811f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_walimu_walimu-fobenu-huvufo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" walimu"," userResponse":" walimu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073215552","data":{"timestamp":" 947073215552"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145115"," gameId":" 72e48d99-3331-4436-a36b-e91e852811f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_rutiza_ravojo-rutiza-rinoke"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" rutiza"," userResponse":" ravojo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073224594","data":{"timestamp":" 947073224594"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145115"," gameId":" 72e48d99-3331-4436-a36b-e91e852811f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_rutiza_ravojo-rutiza-rinoke"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" rutiza"," userResponse":" rutiza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073227080","data":{"timestamp":" 947073227080"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145115"," gameId":" 72e48d99-3331-4436-a36b-e91e852811f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_rutiza_ravojo-rutiza-rinoke"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073250622","data":{"timestamp":" 947073250622"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_145115"," gameId":" 72e48d99-3331-4436-a36b-e91e852811f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.noShow.4__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_rutiza_ravojo-rutiza-rinoke"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}